{
	"description": "Identify what's in the image",
	"type": "url",
	"deck": [
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PuuJVci",	"answers": ["李", "酸桃", "スモモ", "plum", "japanese plum"], "comment": "李（すもも） - (Japanese) plum\n酸桃（すもも） - (Japanese) plum" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/5F2Ta93",	"answers": ["箆鹿", "ヘラジカ", "elk", "moose"], "comment": "箆鹿（へらじか） - elk; moose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/XseXGrS",	"answers": ["川獺", "獺", "カワウソ", "otter"], "comment": "川獺（かわうそ） - otter\n獺（かわうそ） - otter" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/P2kyZmt",	"answers": ["蟻食", "蟻食い", "アリクイ", "anteater"], "comment": "蟻食（ありくい） - anteater" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/8wG1baZ",	"answers": ["穴熊", "アナグマ", "狢", "貉", "ムジナ", "badger"], "comment": "穴熊（あなぐま） - badger\n狢（むじな） - badger" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/qbqDa5P",	"answers": ["鵲", "カササギ", "magpie"], "comment": "鵲（かささぎ） - magpie" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/DguZKv4",	"answers": ["翡翠", "川蝉", "カワセミ", "kingfisher"], "comment": "翡翠（かわせみ） - kingfisher\n川蝉（かわせみ） - kingfisher" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/AjTgmiw",	"answers": ["赤松", "あかまつ", "japanese red pine", "japanese umbrella pine", "tanyosho pine"], "comment": "赤松（あかまつ） - Japanese red pine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mQr8mei",	"answers": ["菖蒲", "あやめ", "iris"], "comment": "菖蒲（あやめ） - (Japanese) iris" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/yBIWGD6",	"answers": ["大葉子", "おおばこ", "plantain"], "comment": "大葉子（おおばこ） - (Asiatic) plantain" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/dtyIOCr",	"answers": ["弟切草", "おとぎりそう", "hypericum erectum"], "comment": "弟切草（おとぎりそう） - hypericum erectum" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/agRd8lB",	"answers": ["鬼胡桃", "おにぐるみ", "japanese walnut", "manchurian walnut"], "comment": "鬼胡桃（おにぐるみ） - Japanese walnut, Manchurian walnut" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/GxqGa04",	"answers": ["橄欖", "かんらん", "chinese white olive"], "comment": "橄欖（かんらん） - Chinese white olive" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/J7eunu5",	"answers": ["燕子花", "杜若", "かきつばた", "rabbit-ear iris", "japanese iris"], "comment": "燕子花（かきつばた） - rabbit-ear iris, Japanese iris\n杜若（かきつばた） - rabbit-ear iris, Japanese iris" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vnI9isA",	"answers": ["桂", "かつら", "katsura", "japanese judas tree"], "comment": "桂（かつら） - katsura, Japanese Judas tree" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mEw3br7",	"answers": ["桔梗", "ききょう", "balloon flower", "chinese bellflower", "platycodon grandiflorum"], "comment": "桔梗（ききょう） - balloon flower, Chinese bellflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/0XiFGiA",	"answers": ["金木犀", "きんもくせい", "fragrant olive"], "comment": "金木犀（きんもくせい） - fragrant olive" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/j0ZkBYf",	"answers": ["樟", "楠", "くすのき", "くす", "camphor tree", "camphorwood", "camphor laurel"], "comment": "樟（くすのき） - camphor tree, camphorwood, camphor laurel\n楠（くすのき） - camphor tree, camphorwood, camphor laurel" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/GKbuPP0",	"answers": ["梔子", "くちなし", "しし", "cape jasmine", "cape jessamine", "gardenia"], "comment": "梔子（くちなし） - gardenia, Cape jasmine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nTbPpOz",	"answers": ["櫟", "橡", "椚", "くぬぎ", "つるばみ", "くのぎ", "sawtooth oak"], "comment": "櫟（くぬぎ） - sawtooth oak" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/brgNB5Y",	"answers": ["栃", "橡", "栃の木", "とちのき", "とち", "japanese horse-chestnut", "japanese horse chestnut"], "comment": "橡（とちのき） - Japanese horse-chestnut\n栃（とちのき） - Japanese horse-chestnut" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/8lWTbur",	"answers": ["黒松", "くろまつ", "black pine", "japanese black pine"], "comment": "黒松（くろまつ） - (Japanese) black pine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/5Lbcsu9",	"answers": ["黒百合", "くろゆり", "black lily", "kamchatka lily", "kamchatka fritillary"], "comment": "黒百合（くろゆり） - Kamchatka lily, Kamchatka fritillary" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PSDalGJ",	"answers": ["月桂樹", "げっけいじゅ", "laurel", "bay laurel", "bay tree", "sweet bay", "laurel tree"], "comment": "月桂樹（げっけいじゅ） - (sweet bay) laurel (tree)" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/41i250C",	"answers": ["欅", "けやき", "槻", "つき", "keyaki", "japanese zelkova"], "comment": "欅（けやき） - keyaki, Japanese zelkova\n槻（つき） - keyaki, Japanese zelkova" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/6vQX1kk",	"answers": ["額紫陽花", "がくあじさい", "紫陽花", "あじさい", "hydrangea", "bigleaf hydrangea", "french hydrangea"], "comment": "紫陽花（あじさい） - hydrangea" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/zAFPRmb",	"answers": ["榊", "さかき", "sakaki"], "comment": "榊（さかき） - sakaki" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/xA6Zpx0",	"answers": ["山茶花", "さざんか", "sasanqua"], "comment": "山茶花（さざんか） - sasanqua" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/NfN6eOp",	"answers": ["百日紅", "猿滑", "さるすべり", "ひゃくじつこう", "crape myrtle"], "comment": "百日紅（さるすべり・ひゃくじつこう） - crape myrtle\n猿滑（さるすべり） - crape myrtle" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/ufhuVxd",	"answers": ["石南花", "石楠花", "しゃくなげ", "rhododendron"], "comment": "石南花（しゃくなげ） - rhododendron\n石楠花（しゃくなげ） - rhododendron" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nfuYyXe",	"answers": ["薺", "なずな", "shepherd's purse"], "comment": "薺（なずな） - shepherd's purse" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Cut4YIC",	"answers": ["棗", "なつめ", "jujube", "chinese date", "red date"], "comment": "棗（なつめ） - jujube, Chinese date, red date" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/6k5Zo3D",	"answers": ["庭漆", "にわうるし", "tree of heaven"], "comment": "庭漆（にわうるし） - tree of heaven" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/aD0ax20",	"answers": ["野薔薇", "のいばら", "のばら", "multiflora rose", "japanese rose", "baby rose"], "comment": "野薔薇（のいばら） - multiflora rose, (Japanese) rose, baby rose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Nz1U71s",	"answers": ["繁縷", "はこべ", "はこべら", "chickweed", "stitchwort"], "comment": "繁縷（はこべ） - chickweed, stitchwort" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/7SxQXfu",	"answers": ["花水木", "はなみずき", "flowering dogwood"], "comment": "花水木（はなみずき） - flowering dogwood" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/hDFxNhi",	"answers": ["柊", "疼木", "ひいらぎ", "ひらぎ", "holly olive", "false holly"], "comment": "柊（ひいらぎ） - holly olive, false holly\n柊木（ひいらぎ） - holly olive, false holly" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/qG3Ff4M",	"answers": ["雛罌粟", "雛芥子", "ひなげし", "red poppy", "common poppy", "coquelicot"], "comment": "雛罌粟（ひなげし） - red poppy, common poppy, coquelicot\n雛芥子（ひなげし） - red poppy, common poppy, coquelicot" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Iaj8PlG",	"answers": ["檜", "桧", "ひのき", "ひ", "hinoki", "hinoki cypress", "japanese cypress"], "comment": "檜（ひのき） - hinoki cypress, Japanese cypress" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/s0J5zux",	"answers": ["昼顔", "ひるがお", "bindweed", "japanese bindweed"], "comment": "昼顔（ひるがお） - (Japanese) bindweed" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/UyquT3N",	"answers": ["夕顔", "ゆうがお", "bottle gourd"], "comment": "夕顔（ゆうがお） - bottle gourd" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/ZmkQvCU",	"answers": ["夜顔", "よるがお", "moonflower"], "comment": "夜顔（よるがお） - moonflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/fRzHAtf",	"answers": ["紅花", "べにばな", "こうか", "safflower", "dyer's safflower", "carthamus tinctorius"], "comment": "紅花（べにばな・こうか） - safflower, dyer's safflower, carthamus tinctorius" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/dUdrV5c",	"answers": ["鳳仙花", "ほうせんか", "garden balsam", "balsam"], "comment": "鳳仙花（ほうせんか） - (garden) balsam" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/3saMIU6",	"answers": ["木槿", "むくげ", "もくげ", "rose of sharon"], "comment": "木槿（むくげ・もくげ） - rose of Sharon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/p4g4l7W",	"answers": ["樅", "もみ", "japanese fir", "momi fir"], "comment": "樅（もみ） - Japanese fir, momi fir" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/RSChT9a",	"answers": ["橅", "山毛欅", "椈", "ぶな", "beech", "siebold's beech"], "comment": "橅（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech\n山毛欅（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech\n椈（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/yFNGWOd",	"answers": ["竜胆", "りんどう", "りゅうたん", "gentian", "autumn bellflower"], "comment": "竜胆（りんどう・りゅうたん） - (Japanese) gentian, autumn bellflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/YyI3tMi",	"answers": ["蓮華草", "れんげそう", "ゲンゲ", "レンゲ", "chinese milk vetch"], "comment": "蓮華草（れんげそう） - Chinese milk vetch" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/BWz1VU7",	"answers": ["水牛", "スイギュウ", "water buffalo"], "comment": "水牛（すいぎゅう） - water buffalo" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/s6i9kkN",	"answers": ["ダックスフント", "ダックスフンド", "犬", "イヌ", "dachshund", "dog"], "comment": "ダックスフント - dachshund" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/SrgARSa",	"answers": ["風信子", "ヒヤシンス", "ふうしんし", "hyacinth"], "comment": "風信子（ヒヤシンス・ふうしんし） - hyacinth" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/bsiz5Z1",	"answers": ["酸漿", "鬼灯", "ほおずき", "ほおづき", "ぬかずき", "かがち", "winter cherry", "chinese lantern plant", "ground-cherry"], "comment": "酸漿（ほおずき） - winter cherry, Chinese lantern plant, ground-cherry\n鬼灯（ほおずき） - winter cherry, Chinese lantern plant, ground-cherry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vtPsdqx",	"answers": ["藤", "ふじ", "wisteria", "wistaria"], "comment": "藤（ふじ） - wisteria, wistaria" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PLoTGJN",	"answers": ["山吹", "やまぶき", "kerria", "japanese yellow rose"], "comment": "山吹（やまぶき） - kerria, Japanese yellow rose" }
	]
}